Harvester: All Ghosts, Spectres and Poltergeists in the hero's army will get to act immediately when combat starts and at the start of each week more of such creatures will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to 0.45*hero level. No extra creatures will be available before level 2. The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.