The hero recieves an amount of random resources every day equal to his Knowledge/2, if the resource type is gold the amount is multiplied by 1000.<br><br><color=orange>Quest<color=white><br>Offer this artifact to a Temple of Shalassa and it will summon a stack of Phoenixes. The size of the stack is equal to 2*amount of weeks passed.<br><br><color=yellow>Backpack<color=white><br>This artifact works from the backpack, but functionality is limited to one artifact per hero.   