Every week the hero receives 1000 gold and an amount of Wood equal to his Knowledge/2.

<color=purple>Cornucopia (1/6)<color=white>
Collect one artifact for every resource type (except gold) and visit an Arcane Library for a unique reward.

<color=orange>Quest<color=white>
Offer this artifact to a Temple of Shalassa and it will summon a pack of Wolves. The size of the stack is equal to 4×amount of weeks passed.

<color=yellow>Backpack<color=white>
This artifact works from the backpack, but functionality is limited to one artifact per resource type per hero.