This creature has a chance of distracting the enemy's attack, directed initially against another friendly stack in its neighborhood, to itself. The trigger chance for this ability is 34% if the targetstack has double the amount of HP before the hit, 39% if the targetstack has the same HP and 52% if the targetstack has half the HP. If the hero has Soldier's Luck skill those chances are 57%,63% and 77%.