There's a chance the enemy attacked by this creature panics and tries to run to the edge of the arena to get as far away from the creature as possible, losing all initiative accumulated by this time. (Doesn't affect creatures immune to Mind-related spells). The trigger chance for this ability is 19% if the targetstack has double the amount of HP after the hit, 22% if the targetstack has the same HP and 31% if the targetstack has half the HP. If the hero has Soldier's Luck skill those chances are 34%,39% and 52%.