This creature's ranged attack ignores 25% of the target's Defense and has an extra chance to thrust the target back one tile and stun it. The trigger chance for this ability is 34% if the targetstack has double the amount of HP before the hit, 39% if the targetstack has the same HP and 52% if the targetstack has half the HP. If the hero has Soldier's Luck skill those chances are 57%,63% and 77%.
