Increases Catapult's Damage from 150-200 to 200-300 and grants it a 30% chance to hit. First Aid Tent healing increases to 10 + 6 HP per hero level (up from 10 + 5). The Ammo Cart increases the Attack of ranged units in the hero's army by 1.<br><color_default>Ballista Damage remains the same as with no mastery and is equal to 3*(A+K) – 4*(A+K), where (A+K) = Hero’s Attack + Knowledge. Each level adds 100 HP and additional Attack and Defense to all War Machines.