Attacking an enemy, this creature has a chance to produce a fire wave dealing physical damage to all enemies in a random radius in the targeted direction. The trigger chance for this ability is 41% if the targetstack has double the amount of HP before the hit, 46% if the targetstack has the same HP and 60% if the targetstack has half the HP. If the hero has Soldier's Luck skill those chances are 65%,71% and 84%.