The lords of Heresh are a cold, grim, and fanatic group.  To climb high in their ranks requires not only talent, but also relentless dedication to the cause of their god, the spider-aspect of Asha.  Arantir has risen high indeed, and counts as one of the greatest ever to live -- or unlive -- among them.  Intense in his beliefs and dedicated to the worship of his goddess and the destruction of her demonic enemies, Arantir is a formidable leader.