Class: Avenger<br>Specialization: Ringleader<br><br><body_bright>At the start of combat additional mana will become available to all friendly Druids (+6) and Elder Druids (+14). Also, at the start of each week more Druids or their upgrades will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to 0.16*hero level. No extra creatures will join before level 4. The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.<br><color_default>Starts with Basic Destructive Magic.