Class: Overlord<br>Specialization: Lizard Breeder<br><br><body_bright>The Lizard Bite ability deals more damage, depending on hero level. The damage is 1.20+0.01*Level times the regular damage (instead of 0.5). Furthermore at the start of each week additional Dark Raiders, Grim Raiders or Brisk Raiders will join the heroes army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to 0.15*Hero Level. No extra creatures will join before level 4. The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.<br><color_default>Starts with Basic Offense.
