Negates enemy Mind Affect immunity. 

<color=teal>Magical Creatures<color_default>
This artifacts also boosts creature summoning in all mage guilds, the artifact works the same as adding an amount of Dragonblood Crystals equal to the knowledge of the hero / 2

<color=yellow>Backpack<color=white>
The second effect also works from the backpack, but functionality is limited to one artifact per hero.