A quantity of native Tier1 & 2 creatures will be resurrected after combat, the amount is at least one or with many casualties equal to 15% + 1% per Knowledge of the Hero. The resurrection requires 4 mana per tier.<color_default><br>
Undead, mechanical and elemental creatures cannot be resurrected. This artifact has no monetary value and is (once) added to the inventory of any hero with the First Aid skill.