Class: Nethermage
Specialization: Lich Queen

<body_bright>At the start of each week additional Liches, Archliches and Lich Masters will join hero army. 
<color_default>The amount is 7% × HeroLevel of creature growth rounded down. The amount is boosted by 40% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero. 

<color=yellow>Starts with:
Advanced Necromancy
Basic Occultism