Class: Demon Lord<br>Specialization: Demonologist<br><br><body_bright>At the start of each week additional Horned Demons, Horned Overseers or Horned Leapers will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to hero level. The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.<br><color_default>Starts with Basic War Machines.