Increases Damage of Ballista to 4*(A+K) – 5*(A+K). Increases Catapult's Damage to 250-400 and grants it a 40% chance to hit. The First Aid Tent heals 10 + 8 HP per hero level. Ammo Cart gains an ability to increase Attack of ranged units in hero's army by 2.<br><color_default>Each level adds 100 HP and additional Attack and Defense to all War Machines. Ballista Damage with no mastery level is 2*(A+K) – 3* (A+K), where (A+K) = Hero’s Attack + Knowledge. Base Catapult Damage is 150-200. First Aid Tent healing with no mastery level = 10 + 5 HP per hero level.