Class: Witch
Specialization: Daughter of Chaos

<body_bright>The hero starts with Destructive Magic and Father Sky grants the witch new destructive magic and adventure spells spontaneously after levelups. Higher level spells can only be learned if the Hall of Trial/Walker's Hut is upgraded. The ability to gain new spells follows random patterns but is not based on chance (by lvl 30 you will have gained all Destructive Magic spells), if the Hall of Trial is upgraded very late the hero will catch up in spells.

<color=yellow>Starts with:
Advanced Runelore
Basic Enlightenment