Fairie Queen: At the start of combat the hero casts Endurance on a friendly stack of Pixies, Sprites or Dryads (ignoring stacks of one unit). The spell costs no mana and the hero's ATB value is reset to a random value between 0.7 and 0.8, but the Swift Mind perk has no effect on this hero. Furthermore, at the start of each week more of such creatures will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to 0.8*hero level. The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.