Class: Conjurer<br>Specialization: Master of the Elements<br><br><body_bright>Every time a friendly stack dies, a group of elementals enters combat at hero's side. Number of elementals increases depending on hero level. In addition the Summon Elementals and Summon Phoenix spells casted by the hero are more powerful, but the hero starts with only one Spellpower and one Knowledge<br><color_default>Starts with Basic Sorcery.