Ossir is an experienced tracker and a prodigy with the bow, arguably the best shot in a nation famed for its talents in archery The respect he commands made him a natural choice when King Alaron was looking for officers, though Ossir would have preferred to remain in his beloved forests. All doubts were dispelled after his first battle, however, as his troops clearly benefited from his leadership.