+1 Spellpower<br><br>
Resurrects a quantity of native Tier7 creatures after combat, the amount is at least one or with many casualties equal to 30% + 1% per Knowledge of the Hero (rounded down for each stack). The resurrection requires 20 mana. <color_default>Undead, mechanical and elemental creatures cannot be resurrected.
<br><color=purple>Garments of the Saint<color_default><br>
-2 Mana Cost of resurrection per artifact (3/7)