Adds +2 to the hero's Attack permanently and a group of War Dancers will join the hero's army immediately. Furthermore, at level 10, one Blade dancer, War dancer or Bladesinger will join the hero's army every day, provided that the hero has some of these creatures in his army already.
<color_default>The number of War Dancers gained immediately depends on the week on which this perk is acquired; it starts at 10 for the first week of the game and increases by 10 every two weeks thereafter, capped at 50 (that is, it stops increasing after Week 1, Month 3).