Class: Engineer
Specialization: Fist Fighter

<body_bright>At the start of each week additional Brawlers, Berzerkers or Battle Ragers will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). 
<color_default>The amount is 7% × HeroLevel of creature growth rounded down. The amount is boosted by 40% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero. 

<color=yellow>Starts with:
Advanced War Machines
Basic Combat