Deirdre was an overzealous Inquisitor for the Church of Light in the Holy Griffin Empire. She spent many years hunting Demon cultists in the Free Cities of the East on the fringe of the Empire’s territory, "cleansing" innocents and culprits alike, worried that a lapse of her vigilance would allow the corruption to spread. In the end, when she was captured and tortured to death by her enemies, her restless soul was spirited away by Necromancers who coveted her knowledge.  Now converted to the Necromancer's cause, it can be argued that no being, living or unliving, knows more about screams than Deirdre.