Souldrinker: The Weakness spell does not only lower creature's damage, but also reduces the target's Defense by an amount equal to Hero Level/3, rounded up. 
<color_default>The Defense decrease lasts for the duration of the spell, and is not cumulative. The effect is lost if the spell is replaced by a Curse spell cast by a creature.
<color=yellow>Starts with:
Advanced Leadership
Basic Dark Magic