This creature has a chance to put an enemy into deep slumber for 1.5 turns. The sleeping enemy is not able to move or attack until it wakes up or it is attacked. Moreover, it gets maximum damage from the Vampire Prince’s attack and it does not retaliate to the attack that wakes it up. This ability will not work on Undead, Mechanical or Elemental creatures. The trigger chance for this ability is 41% if the targetstack has double the amount of HP after the hit, 46% if the targetstack has the same HP and 60% if the targetstack has half the HP. If the hero has Soldier's Luck skill those chances are 65%,71% and 84%.