The hero becomes a mentor. When a mentor meets another friendly hero, the latter gains as much additional experience as needed to have his or her total experience become equal to 10% of that of the mentor's.<br><br><color=red>Complex Knowledge<br><color_default>This skill is very hard to unlearn and attempting it will leave the mind of the hero with permanent scars reducing all primary skills by -2.