When attacking, this creature has a chance of damning the target, resulting in all Fire damage suffered by it being doubled within a certain period of time. The trigger chance for this ability is 27% if the target stack has double the amount of HP after the hit, 31% if the target stack has the same HP and 43% if the target stack has half the HP. If the hero has Soldier's Luck skill those chances are 47%,53% and 67%.