Class: Death Knight<br>Specialization: Vampire Princess<br><br><body_bright>At the start of each week additional Vampires, Vampire Lords or Vampire Princes will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to 0.2*hero level. No extra creatures will join before level 3. The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.<br><color_default>Starts with Advanced Offense.