Goblin King: At the start of each week additional Goblins, Goblin Trappers or Goblin Witch-doctors will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). 
<color_default>The amount is 7% × HeroLevel of creature growth rounded down. The amount is boosted by 40% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.
<color=yellow>Starts with:
Advanced Blood Rage
Basic Combat