Special combat ability. Deals heavy damage to all of the summoned or gated stacks, equal to 40*(Hero Level) + Mastery, where the Mastery starts at 0 for no Summoning Magic mastery and grows by 10 for each level of mastery, up to 30 for Expert Summoning Magic.<br><br><color=orange>Sar-Elam's Disciple<color_default><br>
The hero becomes a strict follower of the Seventh Dragon, who saved Ashan by banishing all demons. The hero discovers 12 Dragonblood crystals.