The hero can teach spells to other heroes and learn from them. Additionaly, the hero will gain a random 4th and 5th circle spell at level 15 and 20 respectively, in every mastered, unsupported magic school.
<color=yellow>Chieftain will also immediately obtain Bloodfire perk once possible.

<color=orange>
Polyglot
<color_default>
The hero speaks many languages which allows him to effectively communicate with all creatures on the battlefield. The hero gets +1 Morale for each unique faction represented in their army.