Seduced and turned to the Necromancer ideals by Sandro himself, this ex-Bull Duchy countess immediately showed thirsts for both blood and power. Already a talented courtesan when still alive, Lucretia's vampiric embrace granted her a couple of centuries to hone her natural gifts for seducing, backstabbing, and politicking.  Promoted to the rank of Undead Princess, she is a spiritual and (im)moral leader to other vampires that dream of re-creating her escapades.