Class: Knight<br>Specialization: Infantry Commander<br><br><body_bright>All Footmen, Squires and Vindicators in the hero's army gain +1 to their Attack and Defense for every two levels of the hero, starting on first level. Also at the start of each week more swordsman will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to 0.25*hero level. No extra creatures will join before level 3. The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.<br><color_default>Starts with Basic Combat.