Class: Flamekeeper<br>Specialization: Lord of the Fissure<br><br><body_bright>All Fire Dragons, Magma Dragons and Lava Dragons in the hero's army will get to act immediately when combat starts. Also, at the start of each week more of such creatures will be available for recruitment in all owned Fortress towns. The amount is equal to 0.04*hero level. There are no extra creatures available before level 13.<br><color_default>Starts with Basic Occultism.