Coven Mistress: Shadow Witches, Shadow Matriarchs and Shadow Mistresses have a chance to make a free additional shot at the hero's current target. The chance is 30%+Hero Level*1% and can apply to multiple stacks. The shot uses one ammunition, and can trigger on damaging and cursing spells, even if an enemy is adjacent. It triggers on the unit under the cursor if a mass spell with area effect is used. If the spells is redirected by magic mirror, the witches shoot at the redirected target (even if themselves).