Class: Trickster
Specialization: Coven Mistress

<body_bright>Shadow Witches, Shadow Matriarchs and Shadow Mistresses have a chance to make a free additional shot at the hero's current target. The chance is 30% + HeroLevel and can apply to multiple stacks. 
<color_default>The shot uses one ammunition, and can trigger on damaging and cursing spells, even if an enemy is adjacent. It triggers on the unit under the cursor if a mass spell with area effect is used. If the spells is redirected by magic mirror, the witches shoot at the redirected target (even if themselves).


<color=yellow>Starts with:
Advanced Luck
Basic Dark Magic