+33% Damage to Fire Spells<br><br>A quantity of Fire Elementals can be resurrected after combat, the amount is at least one or with many casualties equal to 30% + 1% per Knowledge of the Hero (rounded down for each stack). The resurrection requires 10 mana.<br><br><color=orange>Fire Elementals<color_default><br>Throw this artifact in a Fountain of Fortune and it will summon a stack of Fire Elementals. The size of the stack is equal to 4*amount of weeks passed.