The hero loses -2 Attack by carefully preparing the position of his army on the battlefield. All friendly creatures while discharging the Defend command will retaliate pre-emptively (but once as usual) against any enemy that assaults them, but not if the enemy has the "No enemy Retaliation" ability.<br><color_default>Moreover, if the defending friendly creature has "Unlimited Retaliation" ability, it will retaliate the enemy twice: before and after the offending assault. This applies to Ancient Treants as well.