The hero receives a special combat ability to punish the target enemy creature with a powerful avenging strike if that creature is about to attack, retaliate or cast any spell.<br><color_default>Once declared, the avenging strike is active until the end of combat. Should target creature remain idle or move without attacking, the strike will not be performed. The damage dealt is the same as the hero direct damage, with a +3 bonus to his/her Level for the calculation.The hero can target only one unit at a time. Only half a turn is spent when choosing the target.