At the start of every week, 5 Tier3 creatures will join the heroes army, the hero needs to have some of these creatures in his army.<br><br><color=orange>Regalia of the Legion (1/8)<color=white><br>Collect all Items of the Legion and visit an altar of sacrifice for a unique reward.<br><br><color=yellow>Backpack<color=white><br>This artifact works from the backpack, but not if a better artifact of the same type is available.