Class: Avenger
Specialization: Chosen of Sylanna

<body_bright>At the start of each week additional Green Dragons, Emerald Dragons and Crystal Dragons will join hero army. 
<color_default>The amount is 7% × HeroLevel of creature growth rounded down. The amount is boosted by 40% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero. 

<color=yellow>Starts with:
Advanced Avenger
Basic Combat