A quantity of native Tier3 creatures will be resurrected after combat, the amount is equal to 30% + 1% per Knowledge of the Hero (rounded down for each stack). The resurrection requires 10 mana. Undead, mechanical and elemental creatures cannot be resurrected.<br><br><color=purple>Garments of the Saint (1/5)<color=white><br>Mana cost of resurrection will be reduced by -2 per item if the hero carries at least 3 Garments of the Saint.