Negates enemy magic resistance. Magic immunities, if any, are not affected and still remain.

<color=purple>Sar-Issus Regalia (1/4)<color=white>
Spellpower and mana of creatures in hero's army is doubled for wearing at least two of Sar-Issus Regalia. The hero receives an additional +4 Spellpower for wearing all pieces.

<color=orange>Quest<color=white>
Bring all of Sar-Issus Regalia to an Astrologer and receive a unique reward.