+1 Defense<br>
Reinforces the hero's army with native Tier3 creatures at the start of every week, provided some are already present. The amount is equal to the hero's Knowledge/2 (or 1).
<br><color=orange>Regalia of the Legion<br><color_default>
Offer all 7 Regalia of the Legion at a Sacrificial Altar for a unique reward.
<br><color=yellow>Backpack<color_default><br>
Reinforcements are also gained when the artifact is unequipped, but not if a higher level Regalia is equipped or in the backpack.