Increases the damage the hero will inflict attacking enemy creatures on the battlefield, with a +3 bonus to his/her Level for damage calculation. If the creature attacked is on the hero's favorite enemy list, then a critical strike will be delivered, doubling the damage and killing at least one creature.<br><color_default>If the calculated damage is less than the creature's current hit points, it will be increased up to that amount.