This creature has a chance to frighten a target and its neighbors by the attack (small creatures are more disposed to fear). In the event of success the attacker gets +1 to it's Morale and +10% to it's Health. The trigger chance for this ability is 34% if the targetstack has double the amount of HP after the hit, 39% if the targetstack has the same HP and 52% if the targetstack has half the HP. If the hero has Soldier's Luck skill those chances are 57%,63% and 77%.