Class: Death Knight
Specialization: Dark Rider

<body_bright>All mage guilds in owned Necropolis towns will summon Black Knights instead of Mummies and the hero will already have 5 Dragonblood Crystals available at the start of the game for the purpose of summoning them. 
<color_default>This specialization only works if the hero is present on the map on day one.

<color=yellow>Starts with:
Advanced Offense
Basic Combat