Class: Nethermage<br>Specialization: Prophet of Asha<br><br><body_bright>The hero will have +1 Luck as long as any Mummies are in his army and the hero will already have 10 Dragonblood Crystals at level 1 for the purpose of summoning them (more Crystals can be gained from perks in Shatter Magic and Summoning Magic). This specialization doesn't work if the hero is hired by another faction.<br><color_default>Starts with Basic Necromancy.