Class: Death Knight
Specialization: Zombie Lord

<body_bright>All Zombies, Plague Zombies and Rot Zombies in the hero's army have increased Attack and Defense by 0.5 × HeroLevel. 
 
 Also at the start of each week more zombies will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). 
<color_default>The amount is 3% × HeroLevel of creature growth rounded down. The amount is boosted by 40% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero. 

<color=yellow>Starts with:
Advanced Offense
Basic Necromancy