Leader of an exploited people, Quroq does not hesitate to use force, guilt, guile, or cruelty to get his way. To him it is a simple matter of efficiency, and no act is considered to be unacceptable in the pursuit of his vision of the Orcish future. He is convinced that other races and peoples will always seek to persecute and enslave the Orc tribes, and he is no stranger to the idea that the best defence is a good offence.