Allows Summon Elemental spell to be equipped. Increases spellpower by +4 when the Summon Elementals spell is cast.<br><br><color=teal>Magical Creatures<color_default><br>If the hero has any Dragonblood Crystals, more creatures will be summoned. The additional amount is equal to the hero's knowledge*2%<br><br><color=yellow>Backpack<color=white><br>The second effect also works from the backpack, but functionality is limited to one artifact per hero.