Class: Wizard
Specialization: Sculpturer

<body_bright>At the start of each week additional Stone Gargoyles, Obsidian Gargoyles or Marble Gargoyles will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). 
<color_default>The amount is 7% × HeroLevel of creature growth rounded down. The amount is boosted by 40% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero. 

<color=yellow>Starts with:
Advanced Artificer
Basic Destructive Magic