Class: Knight<br>Specialization: Beloved of the People<br><br><body_bright>At the start of combat, a stack of friendly Peasants, Conscripts or Militia will use the Dash ability, doubling their initiative for 3 turns (the stack must be larger than one unit). Furthermore, at the start of each week more of such creatures will join the hero's army (provided that some of these creatures are present). The amount is equal to 0.9*hero level. The amount is boosted by 75% for every additional town captured of the same faction as the hero.<br><color_default>Starts with Basic Leadership.