The hero will inflict 50% of normal spell damage against otherwise resistant creatures and also gains +6 Spellpower as long as he/she doesn't learn Destructive Magic.<br><color_default>The irresistable effect works against luck based resistance, magic proof and immunities, but only for damaging spells, mind immunities cannot be overruled. Against 75% magic proof (example), the spell damage will become 25% + (50% of the remaining 75%) = 62.5%.