The hero receives special combat ability to guard any selected creature in his army until the end of combat by inflicting direct damage to every enemy that is attacking (melee) this guarded creature. Does not apply to retaliation strikes.
<color_default>The damage dealt is the same as the hero direct damage, with a +3 bonus to his/her Level for the calculation The hero can protect only one unit at a time. Only half a turn is spent when choosing the protected target.